{
    "subject": "resource/Paul_Verdzekov",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/description",
    "object": "Catholic bishop",
    "human_readable": "Paul Verdzekov's description is that he was a Catholic bishop.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9781622290611267,
            "question": "What is the significance of Paul Verdzekov being described as a Catholic bishop?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7710726857185364,
            "question": "Paul Verdzekov's description mentions his faith. What was it?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7699601054191589,
            "question": "How would you describe Paul Verdzekov's religious identity?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7583968043327332,
            "question": "What was Paul Verdzekov's religious affiliation?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7279118895530701,
            "question": "Was Paul Verdzekov a member of any religious group?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7257391214370728,
            "question": "What position did Paul Verdzekov hold within the Catholic Church?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6999453902244568,
            "question": "What religious title did Paul Verdzekov have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6114053130149841,
            "question": "Can you tell me something about Paul Verdzekov's religious background?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5765200853347778,
            "question": "To which denomination did Paul Verdzekov belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5384380221366882,
            "question": "What is described as being true about Paul Verdzekov's beliefs?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Paul Verdzekov's description is that he was a Catholic bishop.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2279_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which denomination did Paul Verdzekov belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2279_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me something about Paul Verdzekov's religious background?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2279_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What religious title did Paul Verdzekov have?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2279_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2279_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2279_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2279_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2279_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2279_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2279_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2279_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2279_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2279_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2279_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided documents repeatedly refer to Paul Verdzekov as an Archbishop and Bishop, indicating his role within the Catholic Church.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide several references to Paul Verdzekov as the Archbishop of Bamenda, and his role in the Catholic Church. For example, the text states that \"Our Father, Most Rev. Paul Verdzekov has reminded us...\" and \"The ceremony offers a valued moment for the young and the old, the Catholic and the none Catholic to ponder on the life of the late emeritus Archbishop Verdzekov...\". Additionally, the text mentions his appointment as bishop in 1970 and his later retirement. These references suggest that Paul Verdzekov was indeed a Catholic bishop."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents support the triple \"Paul Verdzekov's description is that he was a Catholic bishop.\" The information in the files mentions his roles as Bishop and Archbishop, which confirms his status as a Catholic bishop."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}